In the end, Christ on earth will reign
He will wipe our tears, remove all pain
In the end, death shall be no more
No crying, no sadness to endure
In the end, wrongs will be made right
No more darkness, no more night
The former things have passed away
He’s making all things new that day
In the end, God’s with us
In the end, no more tears
In the end, He walks with us
In the end, no more fears
Bright as crystal, the river of God flows
The tree of life on each side grows
Blessed are the people who wash their robes
To enter God’s city of endless hopes
They’ll worship God and see His face
His name upon them, stamp of grace
No night remains, no lamp or sun
God is their light, His reign’s begun!
In the end, God’s with us
In the end, no more tears
In the end, He walks with us
In the end, no more fears
In the end, God’s with us
In the end, no more tears
In the end, He walks with us
In the end, no more fears
When grief and sorrow pull us down
Behold the end where hope is found
Though trials come and strength grows dim
In the end, we’ll forever be with Him